You know he's not gonna be happy.
No, I suspect he won't.
Only you can decide
what's best for you, Jesse.
Not him, not me.
I'm out.
So, what are you gonna do
with all that money?
Same thing I do with all the other money.
How about you, teenage retiree?
You'll be living the dream.
Not sure I should stick around town.
That's a start.
Nothing really keeping me here.
Where would you go?
If you were me.
- Doesn't matter. I'm not you.
- Seriously, come on.
Like, if you were my age.
Just play along.
Make some conversation.
Alaska.
Yeah?
Yeah, if I were your age, starting fresh,
Alaska.
It's the last frontier.
Up there, you could be anything you want.
Alaska.
Start over.
- Start fresh.
- One could.
Put things right.
No.
Sorry, kid, that's the one thing
you can never do.
Dude, you suck.
This thing's, like, defective and shit.
Think you got Cheeto dust
in the controller.
It's a bad carpenter
that blames his hammer, yo.
Whatever.
You're apexing too early.
I'm apexing at the apex, bitch.
Don't be telling me how to drive and shit.
You couldn't drive a two-button elevator.
You couldn't drive Miss Daisy.
Whatever that means.
You couldn't drive a short bus
full of slow kids to the zoo.
Yeah, because I'd be
too distracted by you.
You'd be sitting up front,
in your special helmet,
trying to hump my leg.
On account you couldn't drive
Thelma and Louise off of that cliff. Apex!
I can't apex more
than I'm already apexing.
You drive like a blind guy with no legs.
Dude, you...
you drive like my dead grandmoms.
That's disrespectful.
Dude, you lost?
Who is it?
Jesse?
I gotta get that car off the street.
What the hell, yo?
Come check out what's on TV.
Man, what's wrong with you?
I ain't watching no TV right now.
It's the news.
Is it true that a military grade firearm
was altered and used
to carry out this attack?
To the best of my knowledge,
it was an M60 machine gun,
which, yes,
that's strictly a military issue weapon.
As to where he could have obtained
such a weapon,
or the so-called "remote control"
aspect of it,
anything I could say at this point
would just be conjecture,
and I'm not going to engage in that. Yes?
Could you tell us more
about this person of interest?
We're hearing a lot
of conflicting information
and I'm unclear whether this person
took part in the killings,
or whether they were, in fact,
I guess the word
we keep hearing is "liberated."
Were they liberated by White
from some sort of captivity?
I'm not prepared,
at this time, to say any more than that.
They're a person of interest and they may
have information relevant to this case,
or other cases the DEA's investigating.
...was, in fact, held in captivity.
What were the motives of his captors?
Can't speculate on that at this time...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa! Jesse!
- Who's there?
- Hey! It's cool man, it's us!
It's us.
It's us, Jesse, you're safe.
My stuff's gonna fit you like a T, yo.
Not like if you had to borrow it
from Sasquatch over here.
Can't help it that I'm sized for love.
Yeah, you go love
all the giraffes you want, bitch.
Me and Jesse are sticking with the ladies.
Yeah, this here's barely worn.
How's this working for you?
Good?
Jesse?
Right on.
Get you some new clothes then.
Shower will make you feel
a whole lot better.
Truth be told,
you look like you're hurting for one.
Church.
No offense.
Got you a clean towel,
the one on the right. Well, kinda.
And feel free to open up
a new bar of Irish Spring, whatever.
It's underneath, you know.
'Cause the old one might have,
like, hairs on it and shit, and uh,
yo, I got Axe body spray,
I got Obsession for Men,
I got Tommy Hilfinger.
Feel free to use any of 'em you want,
you know? Use 'em all.
Obsession's the bomb, yo.
I got it for him for Christmas.
Oh, uh, hey, um...
Maybe don't, like,
shave and whatnot, you know?
Uh, be less recognizable?
Jesse, did they really...
What?
Did they really keep you in a cage?
Yeah!
Woo hoo!
No!
- Whoa, dude. Why'd you...
- Looking sharp, yo.
Yeah, looking sharp.
Feel like a new man?
Yeah. Thanks.
Want a little something,
take the edge off?
No.
Why'd you, uh, turn off the TV?
News that bad?
There's just, uh... a whole lot of it.
Yeah.
I gotta get out of here.
Where to? You got a plan?
Maybe.
Hey, uh, Skinny,
you got a burner you can give me?
Fully charged and clean as a whistle.
First, I gotta get rid of that car.
...to the victims
and his role in their brutal slayings
remains unconfirmed
by federal authorities.
However, APD sources say the suspect
is Jesse Bruce Pinkman,
a local man who was a student of White's
before joining him in the drug trade.
Together, the two were responsible
for the largest methamphetamine
manufacturing operation in US history.
Sources speculate
the two had a falling out,
after which it is believed Pinkman
was manufacturing the drug
- for the group holding him captive.
- Go for Joe.
Police are now on the hunt for Pinkman
and urging the community
to remain vigilant.
They're asking anyone with information
- to contact APD or call Crimestoppers...
- Yeah, I know who this is.
At this point, who doesn't?
Hey.
- Where's the victim?
- It's in the back.
Look, thank you so much
for doing this, Joe.
About the money, if we can maybe...
It's on the house.
Good kid.
Least I can do.
Watch it, bitch!
You gentlemen threw me
plenty of business back in the day.
I got no complaints in that department.
"Magnets!"
Yeah.
That was a good one. So...
Frankly, you know, I can tell you now,
I had zero confidence that
that would work.
None whatsoever, but hey, live and learn.
Joe, what are you doing?
Writing myself a little insurance policy.
You know, strictly precautionary.
Belt and suspenders.
Okay.
All right, mind at ease, think we're good.
Whoa.
Joe! Joe!
Wait.
Joe, what are you doing?
Fleeing, and I suggest you do the same.
LoJack. The company just activated it,
just this minute.
Talk about timing.
- Just...
- Look, Johnny Law is on his way,
as in here, as in now.
So farewell, goodbye, regrets,
etcetera etcetera.
Joe!
Skinny...
Sorry.
Who's got the keys to that car?
Keys!
Yo. Yo! What are you doing?
We gotta get this thing outta here.
Badger, give me the keys to your Fiero.
Why?
You take my car.
I don't even like your car.
Drives like a dick.
Badger drives my T-bird
200, 300 miles away and ditches it.
Think you'll be heading to Mexico?
No, not Mexico.
Right on, even better.
Leave it near the border.
Hide it, kind of,
but, yo, don't hide it so good
the cops can't find it.
Wipe it down for prints,
then hitchhike back.
Do not let nobody see you in that car.
- You, take Badger's Fiero.
- What about this car?
It stays right here.
Ain't like the cops
don't already know where it is.
I'll tell 'em you dropped by,
the two of us smoked a fat bowl,
traded pink slips, then you split.
I always wanted me an El Camino.
And that's church, yo.
I'll pass any lie detector they give me.
It's what's happening.
You got any cash?
Yo. Kick in, bitch.
I'm doing it. Jesus!
Guys, I don't know what to say.
Don't say nothing. Just go.
Seat belt. Speed limit.
You got about three hours
to get this thing down south.
I'll keep my mouth shut till then,
but after that,
they gonna be putting a APB out
on this bitch.
I'll get her there.
Take care of her, Jesse.
She's a special lady.
That right there is a clown car.
No self-respecting outlaw
would ever get caught dead in that thing.
That's why it's perfect, yo. Deep cover.
Vaya con Dios, amigo.
Oh, uh, the El Camino,
let me see the keys.
Hold up.
Just might keep you from getting spotted.
Can't hurt, right?
Yo, Skinny.
Why you doing all this?
Dude...
you're my hero and shit.
Jesse?
You awake?
Yeah.
Everything good?
- Good.
- Great.
You want a cigarette?
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Guy on KOB keeps calling for rain.
What do you think?
Uh, I don't know.
Guy said like
forty percent chance yesterday.
Sixty percent today.
Maybe it was even fifty yesterday.
But so far,
I mean, I... Yeah, I see clouds,
but I wouldn't call 'em rain clouds,
just regular...
regular cloud-clouds.
Anyway, that's what they look like to me.
Yeah, well, those guys aren't...
always that accurate.
Yeah, right.
I'm not putting myself out there
as any kind of expert
or whatnot,
but I do think it's gonna be...
a beautiful afternoon.
Guess what?
We're all alone.
Yeah?
Yeah. Uncle Jack took everybody down
to Elephant Butte,
on account of he got this new Chaparral.
It's pretty bad-ass,
but I told him...
I'm not really big into waterskiing,
plus, somebody's...
gotta take care of you.
Took some convincing, but...
now...
it's just you and me the whole weekend.
And I...
I'd really like your help with something.
So...
I... I hate to be all like...
But we gotta talk ground rules.
Uh, if you tried to, you know, escape,
I'm gonna have to visit the little boy.
It'll basically be...
out of my hands at that point.
Uncle Jack made you that promise,
and he's gonna want to stick to it.
So...
good behavior, right?
Right?
Good.
I appreciate it, Jesse.
Gotta make sure you don't...
draw too much attention.
I'ma do a better job
of keeping you clean from now on, okay?
Promise.
♪ Take a drive along the beach ♪
♪ Or stay at home and watch TV ♪
♪ You see it really
doesn't matter much to me ♪
♪ I'm not talking about moving in ♪
♪ And I don't wanna change your... ♪
Good job.
Hey, check this out.
There's no water in it.
There used to be water in it,
but they took it out
a couple years ago 'cause of...
some insurance thing.
Okay, so,
it's not actually that heavy, but...
try as I might,
I can't ever get this thing on by myself.
What are you better at,
going forwards or backwards?
Okay, well,
let's both go sideways for a while.
Watch your fingers.
I thought maybe I could just
hang it from the ceiling here...
and just drive right under
and drop it in, but my...
landlord didn't really like that idea.
I guess that's good.
I found this thing on Craigslist.
So...
- Yeah.
- So is that what you needed help with?
Part of it.
The drug kingpin once known
throughout the southwest as Heisenberg
may yet claim a final victim.
Texas authorities investigating
the poisoning of a Houston woman
are looking into her possible connection
to Walter White's criminal organization.
The unnamed woman,
who is hospitalized in critical condition,
is not expected to survive.
White, the former Albuquerque
school teacher
who was the subject
of a six-month international manhunt,
was found dead late Tuesday
at the scene of a gang massacre
which claimed the lives of nine people.
The dollar is down today
on the foreign exchange markets
after an extremely turbulent week
for the Euro.
The Dow Jones is down 15 points,
the NASDAQ is down 34 points,
and the S&P 500 is up ten points.
...have been moved indefinitely
after the discovery of asbestos
in 70 percent of the units.
All residents have been
temporarily relocated...
Hey there, look what the cat dragged in.
Did I hear voices?
Were you talking to somebody?
Nope, not that I know of.
Hey there, Lou. What you up to?
A little horticultural maintenance.
This ficus down at your end
has been looking kinda puny.
Gotta keep the thrift bugs off it.
So, is a ficus technically a plant
or a tree?
I'd say it all depends. Um...
Keep in mind you got over 800 species
of the darned thing.
Wow.
Well, all right, Lou, you have a good one.
Yeah. Don't take any wooden nickels.
Oh, man. That guy.
He's not supposed to be home at this hour.
We really lucked out
that he didn't see you.
He's just always lurking around,
being nosy.
I mean, he was in Vietnam,
which I totally respect, but still...
How you like my place?
Yeah, it's... it's nice.
Kinda...
pastel.
- But in a good way.
- Yeah, right?
I was thinking of Easter eggs,
but...
lately, I'm thinking I might like
to try some new paint.
This stuff is starting to feel
pretty tired.
Okay.
Sure, so, you... Is that why I'm here?
You want me to help you paint?
Maybe, yeah, um...
If we have some time left over.
But, first, uh...
Oh, shit!
Jesus!
Todd...
What...
Ah, shit!
Okay, please don't,
you know, make me feel worse
than I already do.
Who is this?
Sonia, my cleaning lady.
And honestly,
I don't feel much like
talking about it, so...
You want to give me a hand, Jesse?
Just keep it straight.
Oh, w... wait.
Unroll it.
Kinda need this.
Okay.
Now, we just gotta wait
for nosy Lou to go bowling.
I think he leaves in like an hour.
You want some soup?
You want soup?
I got chicken noodle, chicken and stars,
cream of chicken.
Bean with bacon.
One left, Jesse.
- What did she do to you?
- What?
Oh, she didn't do anything to me.
Then...
why?
Right there.
That book, if you wanna know so bad.
Uncle Jack taught me
always keep my money close, so...
I have these old World Book Encyclopedias,
the whole entire set.
A to Z.
My grammy gave 'em to me
when I was in middle school,
but I figured...
nobody needs books anymore,
'cause everything's on the computer.
Uh, it seemed like a good hiding place.
Plus, I had all these other volumes
left to fill.
So your cleaning lady
was stealing your money?
What? No.
She was as honest as the day is long.
Like, George Washington honest.
But she found it,
and I can't have anybody finding it.
She brought it straight in here
to show me.
She actually thought
I didn't know it was there.
I just... I wonder what the heck
she was looking up?
She barely spoke any English.
M for Mexico maybe? I don't know.
It's weird.
Where are we gonna... take her?
Someplace pretty.
She deserves that.
Hey, do me a favor
and put that away, would ya?
Just straight down the hall
all the way in the back,
there's a whole shelf of 'em.
Thanks.
Sure you don't want any soup?
How you like my bedroom?
Pretty bitchin', huh?
Be sure to alphabetize them.
I guess I better come up with
a new hiding place for my money.
They got these things called banks.
Actually,
I think I know the perfect spot.
It might take a little engineering, but...
Man, it would be right here
and nobody would ever find it.
"Nothing beats cash on hand,"
that's what Uncle Jack says.
- ...an average kid.
- Yeah.
I mean, he liked to draw.
He was good at that.
When was the last time you saw him?
Uh...
A year. Maybe more. I mean...
it was way before all of this.
Is there anything you wish
you could say to your son right now?
Please...
come forward.
Too many people have...
For your sake, for everybody's sake,
son, turn yourself in.
♪ You're looking kinda lonely, girl ♪
♪ Would you like someone new to talk to ♪
♪ Ah, yeah, all right ♪
♪ I'm feeling kinda lonely too ♪
♪ If you don't mind ♪
♪ Can I sit down here beside you ♪
♪ Ah, yeah, all right ♪
♪ If I seem to come on too strong ♪
♪ I hope that you will understand ♪
♪ I say these things
'cause I'd like to know ♪
♪ If you're as lonely as I am ♪
♪ And if you mind ♪
♪ Sharing the night together ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Sharing the night ♪
♪ We could bring in the morning, girl ♪
♪ If you want to go that far ♪
♪ And if tomorrow finds us together ♪
♪ Right here the way we are ♪
♪ Would you mind ♪
♪ Sharing the night together ♪
♪ Ooh, yeah ♪
You wanna say a few words?
No.
Nice, nice lady.
Excellent housekeeper.
Hey, grab another pack, would ya?
There should be one in the glove box.
You find 'em?
I'll take that, Jesse.
Jesse, I'll... I'll take that.
On the way home,
I was gonna get us some pizza.
A couple large pies.
Maybe a six-pack of beer?
Some ice cold beer.
Does that sound good?
'Cause... 'cause you earned it today.
You definitely did.
What kind of pizza do you like, Jesse?
Jesse, what kind of pizza?
Pepperoni.
Pepperoni. Sure.
Classic. I like that too.
Come on.
Look at that view.
Should be a heck of a sunset.
You know what Uncle Jack says,
"Life is what you make it."
God!
Yeah!
Jesus!
Hello?
Oh, hey. You folks are back, huh?
Wow.
When you search a place,
you really search it.
Sir, what can we do for you?
I'm Louis Schanzer.
I live across the hall, down in unit 11.
I talked to your guys yesterday.
I got a card from one of your sergeants,
and I just want you to know I'm around
if you ever need
any additional information.
Okay. Great.
See, I knew the decedent pretty well,
never really trusted him.
To be honest,
I kinda saw this thing coming.
I mean, well, not exactly, but kinda.
Yeah, great.
Well, we'll definitely keep that in mind.
Yeah. Definitely, thank you.
You guys have business cards?
No, I'm sorry, we're fresh out.
Take it easy.
You too, and hey, listen,
if you ever need any help with this case,
see I've done
a little investigating myself. I...
Unit 11.
Okay.
I'll start here, you start in the back.
Let's meet in the middle.
I mean, Jesus.
Neil, they've tossed the shit
out of this place. What's left to find?
Shut up and look.
Hey, little guy.
Dude's got a tarantula.
Yeah, no crazy in this house.
Perfectly normal.
Oh.
I'm no cop killer.
You be cool...
and I will be cool.
Understand?
Call your partner in here.
Casual, very casual.
Do it.
Hey, Lieutenant.
Lieutenant, you hear me?
Yeah.
Come in here, would ya?
You find something?
Yeah, pretty much.
Lieutenant?
What's waiting for me back there, Casey?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Put your gun down!
- Okay, relax, relax.
Put your gun down
and show me your hands!
Everybody relax.
He says he's not looking
to kill any cops.
So let's just...
let's figure this out, all right?
Let's... We're gonna figure this out.
What are you doing here, Pinkman?
There's something I need.
As soon as I get it, I am gone.
You let me outta here,
I swear I will not hurt this guy.
What's this thing you need?
Seriously, throw your gun in here
and show me your hands.
Seriously, no. You point yours at me,
I point mine at you.
That's how this works.
What's this thing you need?
Look... I don't wanna shoot any cops.
Yeah, you don't wanna shoot any cops.
Great, fantastic.
You know how many officers
we got downstairs?
Tell him, Casey, tell him how many.
A good six, last I counted.
Six my ass,
I counted eight of 'em down there.
Patrol car on all four corners,
more up the street.
They hear shooting,
what do you think they're gonna do?
Oh, they're coming up.
They're coming up, guaranteed.
That's right, they're coming up.
Then how far do you think
you're gonna get?
There's only one choice here, buddy.
And you know what it is.
Come on.
Nobody wants to hurt you.
Give up, Pinkman.
It's your only chance.
On the ground. Guns down.
On your stomach.
Jesus Christ! Are you kidding me?
Are you kidding me?
- What now?
- Stay on him.
All right.
Hey! What are you doing?
Shut up.
Hey, how about some handcuffs, yo.
What are you doing?
You two aren't cops.
You...
Shut the fuck up.
His legs! Get his legs.
Find me something to gag him with.
No!
I know where the money is.
That's what you're here for, right?
You picked up a couple of windbreakers
at the Army & Navy store,
came strolling in, all clever and shit.
Well, I know where it is.
And I guaran-fucking-tee
you won't find it on your own.
Detectives? Louis Schanzer, unit 11.
I got somethin' that might be helpful.
Hello?
Detectives? Everything okay?
Uh, sorry about that, sir. We're...
dusting for fingerprints, you know?
It's a delicate process.
I thought your CSI boys do that.
Didn't they get 'em all yesterday?
Yeah, well, you know, sometimes,
you want something done right...
Oh, God, tell me about it.
My line was restaurant
and hospitality supplies,
so I completely get it.
Hey, listen, I just came across
an old note Todd Alquist wrote me.
- Figured it may be of interest.
- Oh, really?
Yeah.
Sort of a half-assed apology
he slipped under my door.
I'd gone to our landlord
about this stupid truck cap of his
everybody kept tripping over, and...
Well, anyway, if you need
a handwriting sample for analysis.
That's... Yeah, yeah, that could be...
- Yeah, sure.
- Left it inside.
Didn't want to touch it,
speaking of fingerprints.
You're welcome to come examine it.
Oh, it's no trouble. I got time.
Show me the money, I let you go.
Hey.
What do you say, huh?
Seems pretty fair to me.
Oh, shit!
- Holy shit!
- Keep your voice down.
God, there's gotta be...
there's gotta be a million here. Yeah.
What are you doing?
- Taking my half.
- Wow.
Yeah?
A little man with big dreams? Yeah?
Hey, if I were you,
I'd walk the hell outta here right now.
I'll shoot you, you son of a bitch.
I will shoot you.
Then do it already.
If I don't get this money,
I am dead anyway.
All right? If you pull that trigger,
then you are gonna have to kill
that loudmouth down the hall
and every other witness in the place.
Then you will be as fucked as I am.
So...
what's it gonna be?
Three-way split. And you got your third.
Don't push it.
- Yep?
- Don't react, just listen.
I got the money.
You gotta keep him talking
for the next five minutes.
Since I got the Brita,
I find the tea tastes noticeably better.
Not a problem.
You got balls, I'll give you that.
Can I get my gun back?
Fuck you. Go buy one.
I was wondering
when you were gonna remember me.
It's colorful, I'll say that much.
Yes, it is.
Uh, I don't expect
you'd ever lose it in your closet.
Mm. And no dirt bag to replace?
That's correct.
A lot of our customers find that handy
and practical.
But they want an arm and a leg
to pay for it.
And I ain't paying for no paint job.
Yes, I agree. It's very expensive.
But it's a fine product.
However, if you are in love
with your Kirby,
I'll bet I could get it
working for you again.
Uh, be with you in a minute.
Fixing my Kirby,
how much would that cost?
Well, I won't know
until I take a good look at it, and it...
and if it needed a new motor,
it'd be a little bit expensive,
but certainly not as expensive
as a new Dyson.
The estimate's free, and...
all you gotta do is bring it in here.
- I may take you up on that.
- Excellent.
If I can get my niece to help me.
They make 'em so heavy.
Yes, they do,
and I want you to promise
you won't try to bring it in by yourself.
- Get that help.
- Hm.
I just don't know why they can't
make things to last anymore.
Oh! You're singing my song.
I want you to have a great day now.
Thank you, thanks for your help.
I'll be back with my Kirby.
Excellent. Drive carefully.
If there's any questions I can answer,
just let me know.
I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't do that.
I'm open for business.
Um, I'm looking for a...
Hoover Max.
Pressure Max, Max Pressure.
Hoover, or maybe it's a Pro Max.
Got like a... like a filter.
Hoover products are right over there
on the wall behind you.
Look, I don't remember
the exact, like, password.
All right? But it was a vacuum thing.
Okay, fine.
Here you go.
Four...
six...
ten...
fourteen,
sixteen, eighteen,
twenty, twenty-two...
twenty-four, twenty-five.
There you go.
$125,000.
Come on, man, you know why I'm here.
I can't say I do, no.
Yeah, you do. You're the guy.
Yeah, you do.
You're the guy.
Look, I am 96 percent sure
that you are the guy,
so why don't you just, like, admit it?
Look, all right, no wire.
Okay? No wire.
And no gun.
Okay? And nobody knows I'm here.
I just need...
just need your services.
The day at the pickup spot,
you pulled up in a minivan,
a red Toyota minivan.
Looks like a kidney bean.
Same exact minivan
you got parked out back.
All right? I saw it.
All right.
You got rules. All right.
I get that, and I apologize, seriously.
I didn't go with you that day,
and I am sorry.
Look, you will never know how sorry,
but I am here now.
All right? And I have cash.
So, please?
Okay?
Please?
- You owe me for that first pickup.
- Yes!
You're the gu...
- Wait, what?
- This...
is previously-owed.
Going forward,
were we to,
would require an additional 125.
All right.
Fair is fair.
A deal's a deal.
All right. Look...
Four...
eight...
ten,
fourteen, eighteen...
twenty...
Twenty-two.
Yeah.
Twenty-three.
By my arithmetic, you're $10,000 shy.
Eighty-two hundred.
May I borrow this?
What are you doing?
I'm gathering your belongings.
No, no no. No, no. Stop.
I'm not gonna try to collect
what you owe me.
I don't think it would end well
for either one of us.
This is not an inconsequential
amount of money.
Hey, listen to me.
Spend it wisely,
it will last you for years.
Please, you don't understand.
Keep a low profile, travel by night.
Oh, God.
With a little luck,
you will soon find yourself
many miles from here.
Godspeed to you.
So that's it?
That's it.
Now, please leave.
You are going to jack me up
over a measly $1,800?
I've got to reopen.
The longer you stick around here,
the more you jeopardize yourself.
No, hey...
No. Hey...
Have you been watching the news?
I have. Very much so.
So you hear
what they've been saying about me.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Look, these people,
they have kept me in a concrete hole.
Look, I don't even know what month it is.
They made me watch when they...
when they shot someone...
If you believe that you can
pull on people's heartstrings,
you should take your chances
with the police.
From where I sit, you made your own luck.
As did your former partner.
As did your lawyer.
You said it yourself, a deal's a deal.
No.
I am not going anywhere.
I am staying right here
until you help me.
What are you doing?
Hi, yes.
There's a young man in my store,
and he refuses to leave.
Hey, stop.
I...
- Yeah, he might be armed.
- Stop it.
Uh, not overtly.
But, yes,
I'm beginning to feel threatened.
- Are you serious?
- Sure.
My name is Ed Galbraith.
I own Best Quality Vacuum,
2714, 4th Street.
Northwest. That's correct.
I would appreciate it very much
if you'd send someone immediately.
You are so full of crap.
You didn't call anybody just now.
You faked it.
And you wanna know how I know?
You got as much to lose as I do.
More. Way more.
When your "cops" get here
and they bust me,
first question they're gonna ask
is what am I doing here,
trying to hand over
a Hefty bag full of cash
to a dude who runs
a vacuum cleaner store.
What comes out then? Huh?
Oh, and you, uh, wanna know
what else is bullshit?
You know, like, word to the wise:
next time to try to pull this shit
on someone,
you don't just hang up on a 9-1-1 call.
They won't let you.
Because the lady, or dude, or whoever
is like, "Stay on the line with me, sir.
Stay on the line
until the officers arrive."
And if you did hang up,
they'd call you back immediately.
But, hey, guess what?
Seriously, yo. Pathetic.
Wow, you gotta love that response time.
Take your money.
Officers, thank you very much
for getting here so fast.
- He obviously heard my call and...
- Is he still here?
No, he's not, he's gone. I, uh...
Uh, he was spooked by my phone call
and he headed up northbound, uh...
on foot maybe 30 seconds ago.
- Can you describe him?
- Uh, sure I can.
He was, uh...
young, uh, he's white,
skinny, very tall guy.
Six-five, six-six.
Had a tattoo over his right eyebrow.
Interesting. A large insect.
Best Quality Vacuum, how may I help you?
A deal's a deal? Your word is your bond?
It is.
I'll get you your money.
Hello?
Hey, Mom.
Jesse?
It's Jesse.
Give me... Give me the phone.
Jesse, is that you?
Hey, Dad. Yeah, it's me.
How the both of you doing?
We've been better.
Yeah.
How's Jake? Can I say hi to him?
Jake's on a band trip to London,
thank God...
Jesse, where are you?
I heard you saying
that I should turn myself in.
Yes. It's the right thing to do.
Quit running and get some help.
No one is trying to hurt you, son.
Better you come forward on your own,
it'll be safer for you, better all around.
You remember where
we used to have those picnics?
All those years ago?
By the little lake,
the one with all the ducks?
Yeah?
Do you think you guys
could come get me maybe?
- We're on our way.
- Hey.
And, uh...
it's probably too late to say this...
I don't know if it'll mean much to you...
but you did your best.
And whatever happened with me...
it's on me.
Okay?
Nobody else.
We're heading northbound on 12th,
about to turn left on Lomas.
- Be sure to stay on the house.
- Will do.
Jake's birthday.
Yeah. Yeah.
And then after that,
it's the first turn off Broadway.
No, then you're gonna go ahead
and look for...
Nah, man, don't go by junkyards.
There's like 50 junkyards.
The rebar place is what...
Yeah, the re...
Yeah, exactly.
That's the one.
Turn there.
Yeah. Straight down on the right.
Look for the sign.
Oh, yeah, I got you.
They're here!
Woo hoo! All right!
Yeah, okay. Oh, my God.
Yeah.
Woo!
- Keep your mouth shut.
- All right.
- Oh, shit.
- That's a big, big boy.
This guy's bigger than your mom, Sean.
Who's Kandy?
Yeah, that's me.
- The car's too small for you.
- $750 an hour, cash up front.
- Oh, man.
- The perks are extra.
Well, by all means.
- I get the first perk.
- We want the perks.
Perks, perks! Yeah!
- Don't we, boys? Yeah?
- We want the perks!
- Perks!
- Got any perks in there?
Oh, my God!
That's what I'm talking about.
- Gentlemen, hi.
- That's a good start. And hello to you.
- Hello to you.
- Hi, welcome.
- Where have you been all my life?
- Excuse me.
Oh, just waiting for you
in this little car.
- Oh, I'm here, baby, don't worry.
- Please, come right this way.
Careful, careful now.
Should've brought your work boots.
Well, nobody told me
it was gonna be yucky.
My name is Casey.
I never really go for redheads.
All right.
Done.
Bullshit you're done.
You've been here 20 minutes,
what'd you do?
Added a fishplate up here,
one in the middle, one down at the end.
Added a what?
A fishplate.
What, like a... plate of fish?
What the fuck is that?
Is that even a real word?
Look, man, I want more of those things,
the sideway diagonal things,
like twice as many.
Those are gussets.
You got enough of 'em already.
Okay, yeah. So, gussets I got out the ass,
but a fishplate I need 'cause... What?
I'm Catholic and it's Friday?
You sure you couldn't just
put a few more gussets up there, Neil?
I mean, what could it hurt, right?
Hey, it's your money.
But what I just did,
you don't even need that.
I told you I built this thing right.
Look, bro, I'm not like impugning
on your precious welding skills.
It's just we have a, uh,
unique situation here.
Tried to rabbit on us once already.
I'm thinking he's gonna figure out a way
to break this thing.
You kidding me?
Him?
Yeah, it's just I kinda feel it flexing
a little bit. A bit right here, look.
Yeah, see? Right there.
Yeah, a little bit.
Yeah, I don't see jack shit flexing.
That's four-inch channel iron up there.
You could hang an F150 from it
and shove it back and forth
like a beach ball.
It's going nowhere.
Okay, you and your big four inches.
It's just this little bastard's wiry.
I don't care how wiry he is.
Have him knock himself out.
Oh, yeah?
Wanna put your money
where your mouth is?
Fifty bucks says he breaks this thing
right here, right now.
Fifty, plus,
then you gotta put up more of those...
What'd you call 'em, gussets?
No charge.
Throw in some fishplates too,
while you're at it.
You're on.
- I'm on, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
All right, all right.
Get that shit out the way and watch this.
All right, good-lookin'.
This is it. This is the acid test.
Go for it.
Now! Go, go, go! Come on!
Faster! Hit it hard!
All right, all right.
Other way, other way.
Hey, what are you slowing down for?
Hit it!
All right, come on, get up.
I got 50 bucks riding on you.
I gotta eat this month.
Kenny, if he breaks his leg,
he's not gonna be able to cook.
What, are you the fucking HR department?
Jesus, Toddie, relax.
We're gonna even up the odds a little bit.
All right.
Okay.
Now, I believe in you.
You're gonna John Henry this bitch, yeah?
Now go.
Go, go, go! Let's go!
Go, go, go, go! Yeah!
Woo!
All right, other way. Faster!
Hit it hard!
Yeah, baby!
Yeah! Caught some air.
Yeah!
Todd, who is this guy anyway?
What'd he do?
Uh...
It's... It's kind of a long story.
Yeah.
He's a rat.
That's all you need to know.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hey, hey!
- Okay, guys.
- We dancing or what?
- You paid till three
and it's five past.
Hell, I'll go another hour.
Come on, we all will.
Where you going? Huh?
- Come on.
- Wanda!
Hey, Wanda!
Wanda!
Would you stop? You're crazy.
Ya Opie-lookin' self.
- We'll see you next week.
- In your dreams, buddy.
Just wanna go home, get in my bed,
cuddle with my dog.
I am exhausted.
I'm never coming back
to this dump place again.
My feet hurt.
Wake up, Clarence, let's go.
Look at my fucking shoes. I know.
This is a mess.
It wasn't even worth it.
It's gonna take me hours
to get the mud out.
Wait for me!
I said, "My son,
cocaine wasn't even invented
when Brigham Young was born.
It's okay, you can have some."
Come on, come to papa. There we go.
- You'll never get that back.
- There he goes.
- Black diamond.
- Bye-bye, cocaine.
He's all cocaine and Mormons.
♪ I ain't got me nobody ♪
♪ I don't carry me no load ♪
What's up?
I need more money.
Oh, yeah?
That three-way split
didn't quite cover it for me.
I'd appreciate you helping me out.
Well, what's he talking about?
Three-way split?
You mean there was a third more?
And you gave it to him?
It's a long story.
Well...
What long story?
When I left,
he didn't even have a fucking gun.
Well, he's got one now, doesn't he?
So, you know, shut up. Let me handle this.
Neil, who the hell is this guy?
Yeah, I can't believe you just
let him walk in here with...
"Shut up" means everybody.
Now,
how exactly do you plan
on pulling this off?
I mean, being that there's five of us
and one of you.
I'm not here to rob you.
Oh, you're not?
Then how's this work?
All I need is $1,800.
I'm asking as a...
a favor.
Oh, what, like charity?
Seems to me this silly son of a bitch
already forked over, big time.
Casey, seriously, shut up.
$1,800, huh?
Why not an even two grand?
You know, nice round number.
$1,800 is all I need.
So, what's the gun for?
It's like personal protection?
I mean, is that a...
What is that? Let me see that thing.
Show me.
Oh, my God, is that a .22?
You brought a .22?
Jesus!
Where'd you get that thing?
I think it was my grandfather's.
Oh, well, it's adorable.
I know we got empty beer cans around here
if you wanna do some plinking?
Eighteen hundred.
I'm gone forever.
Simple as that.
Neil, I swear to God, if you give
this piece of shit one more dollar...
Cold out here.
Tell you what.
My third is in a duffel bag
in the top drawer of that file cabinet.
Where's yours?
In my car.
Parked up the street.
What do you say...
your .22...
against my .45?
Winner takes all.
- Like the Wild West?
- Yeah.
Like the Wild West.
What? Come on.
Jesus! Neil?
- Come on, man, I didn't mean this...
- Casey.
Shut the fuck up.
- I'm not gonna get in another...
- No, wait, you go... Oh!
Shoot!
You ready?
Yeah.
Hey, don't shoot.
All right. Get over here.
- Please.
- All right, get up!
All right.
Give me your license.
- Driver's license, do it!
- Yes.
I got kids.
Like I give a shit.
All right.
Sean,
Kyle,
Colin.
I know where you live.
You tell the cops about me,
and I am coming
for every goddamn one of you.
- You understand?
- Yeah.
Go.
Go!
Dude, you're on fire.
Ah.
Of course I miss you.
Yeah? Well...
do you miss me?
I don't know.
How you...
How are you gonna convince me?
Yeah, bitch.
- Ah.
- Thank you.
Leave the pitcher, would ya?
- Sorry, can't really do that.
- W... wait.
Sure you can.
Wow.
- It's like I'm here with Sinatra.
- I know, right?
Certainly went big with the pineapple.
Only an asshole doesn't like pineapple.
Guessing you don't?
I can take it or leave it.
Pineapple's good for you.
It's got bromide.
Bromelain.
But, close.
Actually, it's not close at all.
Are you gonna eat?
You should really eat something.
No, I'm eating. I'll eat.
Gotta eat, gotta hydrate.
Get those electrolytes
you were talking about.
- Your sodium, you know, all that shit.
- Good, yeah.
Yeah.
Hey.
- He's all right.
- I'm fine, thank you.
- You all right?
- I'm fine. Good.
- Sit down.
- All right.
How long will it take to sell this batch?
- Six months.
- Jeez...
Easy. Maybe more.
There's no one that you can think of
who might...
buy the entire amount?
Uh, someone with a spare $1.3 million
lying around? No.
Can't say that I do.
Your family is gonna get every dime
they got coming to them, Mr. White.
No matter how long it takes.
- Hydrate. Seriously.
- Yeah.
What about you, Jesse? Hm?
- Huh?
- After this. What then?
Nothing? What about college?
No, what is stopping you
from going to college?
Um...
- Nothing, I guess.
- Yeah, nothing at all.
- Say you went to college.
- Uh-huh...
What would you study, you think, eh?
What interests you?
Sports Medicine?
Sports Medicine.
Yeah.
That's... Yeah, sure. That's...
- Yeah.
- ...could...
Or... Business. Hm?
Business and Marketing.
You could practically teach that class.
- Well, yeah.
- I mean, you'd be a natural.
And with a Business degree,
I mean, that's handy anywhere.
Yeah.
- Yeah, I guess that could be cool.
- Yeah.
You could do it too.
First step,
get your GED, that's no problem.
What do I need a GED for?
I got my diploma.
Oh.
Of course, yeah, right.
Right, right, right.
Yo, you were standing right on stage
when they handed it to me.
I know, it just slipped my mind.
I totally graduated high school, dick.
- Which is no thanks to you, all right?
- Just stay on the subject here.
All right?
The larger point being...
You know, look, forget it.
I... I don't have a larger point.
- I'm just making conversation.
- Yeah.
Hm.
You're really lucky, you know that?
You didn't have to wait your whole life
to do something special.
This is Alaska.
Forty miles in that direction
gets you to Haines.
It's quiet.
Yeah.
Figured you could use some of that.
All right.
Date of birth?
06/10/84.
- Mother's maiden name.
- Stackhouse.
Where was she born?
Kadena Air Force Base, Okinawa, Japan.
Father's date of birth.
02/07/51.
Your father's second to the last job.
Claims adjuster, Dairyland Insurance,
Appleton, Wisconsin.
What's your social security number?
141-18-6941.
Backward.
1496-81-141.
All right.
Daylight's burning,
you know where you're going.
Anything else?
Hold on a sec.
Seal this up, please.
I'm going to Mexico City in about a month.
I'll mail it from there.
Anyone else you wanna say goodbye to?
Not many of us
get a chance to start fresh.
Good luck, Mr. Driscoll.
I was thinking about that thing
you said about the universe.
Going where the universe takes you?
Right on.
I think it's a cool philosophy.
I was being metaphorical.
It's a terrible philosophy.
I've gone where the universe takes me
my whole life.
It's better to make those decisions
for yourself.
♪ 3:00 a.m. I'm awakened ♪
♪ By a sweet summer rain ♪
♪ Distant howling of a passing ♪
♪ Southbound coal train ♪
♪ Was I dreaming ♪
♪ Or was there someone just lying here ♪
♪ Beside me in this bed? ♪
♪ Am I hearing things? ♪
♪ Or in the next room ♪
♪ Did a long forgotten music box
just start playing? ♪
♪ And I know ♪
♪ It's a sin putting words
in the mouths of the dead ♪
♪ And I know ♪
♪ It's a crime to weave your wishes
into what they said ♪
♪ And I know ♪
♪ Only fools venture
where them spirits tread ♪
♪ 'Cause I know ♪
♪ Every word
Every sound bouncing 'round my head ♪
♪ Is just static on the radio ♪
♪ Static on the radio ♪
♪ Just static on the radio ♪
♪ Everything I think I know ♪
♪ Is just static on the radio ♪
♪ Static on the radio ♪
♪ Everything I think I know ♪
♪ Is just static on the radio ♪
♪ Midnight rendezvous with a pretty girl ♪
♪ Wearing a torn and tear-stained gown ♪
♪ Like a ghost ship
she appeared from nowhere ♪
♪ On a lonely highway
and flagged me down ♪
♪ I gave her a lift downtown
to the Greyhound station ♪
♪ And in the flicker of the neon lights ♪
♪ She kissed me goodbye
And in the mirror of her eyes ♪
♪ I saw my own reflection ♪
♪ And I know ♪
♪ The blind will sometimes
lead the blind ♪
♪ And I know ♪
♪ Through shadow lands
and troubled times ♪
♪ And I know ♪
♪ Forsaking love, we seek the signs ♪
♪ Of truths forever hid behind ♪
♪ The static on the radio ♪
♪ Static on the radio ♪
♪ Everything I think I know ♪
♪ Is just static on the radio ♪
♪ Static on the radio ♪
♪ Everything I think I know ♪
♪ Is just static on the radio ♪
♪ Now there's a church house
About a stone's throw down ♪
♪ From this place where I been staying ♪
♪ It's Sunday morning
and I'm sittin' in my truck ♪
♪ Listening to my neighbor sing ♪
♪ Ten years ago I might have joined in ♪
♪ But don't time change those inclined ♪
♪ To think less of what is written ♪
♪ Than what's wrote between the lines? ♪
♪ 'Cause I know ♪
♪ Dreams are for those
who are asleep in bed ♪
♪ And I know ♪
♪ It's a sin putting words
in the mouths of the dead ♪
♪ 'Cause I know ♪
♪ For all my ruminations
I can't change a thing ♪
♪ Still I hope ♪
♪ There's others out there
that are listening ♪
♪ To the static on the radio ♪
♪ Static on the radio ♪
♪ Everything I think I know ♪
♪ Is just static on the radio ♪
♪ Static on the radio ♪
♪ Ain't praying for miracles ♪
♪ I'm just down on my knees ♪
♪ Static on the radio ♪
♪ Listening for the song behind ♪
♪ Everything I think I know ♪
♪ Static on the radio ♪
♪ Everything I think I know
♪ Is just static on the radio ♪
♪ Everything I think I know ♪